



216.375.8577



julie.sasak.design@gmail.com



juliesasak.squarespace.com



linkedin.com/in/julie-sasak

EDUCATION

Cuyahoga Community College

Parma, OH 2015 Certificate of Graphic Design

Kent State University

Kent, OH 2012

Bachelor of the Arts

SKILLS

Adobe Illustrator Adobe InDesign **Adobe Photoshop Apparel Printing** Creativity **Customer Service Custom Design** Logo Design Mac & PC Efficient Marketing Design **Microsoft Office Problem Solving Photo Editing Production Art** Time Management **Typography** Wilcom TrueSizer Wordpress

PERSONAL PROFILE

Graphic designer with 6 years of professional experience who has a passion for bringing communication design to life. An organized and highly creative individual who possesses the ability to create unique and precise design work. Known for being hardworking, friendly and dependable.

EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCE

BSN SPORTS, McCLELLAN PARK CA

September 2019 - Present *Graphic Designer*

Designer at a fast paced and high-volume athletics apparel company. Creates new art and prepares graphics for screen print and embroidery production using Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop and TrueSizer Pro. Works closely with sales managers to deliver exceptional quality artwork to our customers within a 24 hour turn-around time.

LODI WINEGRAPE COMMISSION, LODI CA

October 2018 - July 2019

Graphic Designer and Educational Outreach Assistant

Graphic Designer and assistant to the educational outreach program. Responsible for preparing and designing content for email blasts, postcards, newsletters, branding guides, a directory, and other communications. In charge of updating website content, weekly blog posts, and all social media accounts. Attended and prepared materials for meetings and events.

UNIVERSITY TEES, LAKEWOOD OH

July 2016 - October 2018

Junior Designer

Designer at a custom apparel company specializing in creating and preparing artwork for embroidery and screen print production. Provided custom made and templated designs to clients while maintaining a 3 day turn around time for all new artwork and revisions.

- Recognized for maintaining a less than 3 percent error rate for all design orders.
- Promoted to lead embroidery artist, resulting in an improvement to the production process by maintaining a high standard of consistency and accuracy.